import { Question } from "../components/MovieQuiz";

export const vincenzoData: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "What is Vincenzo Cassano's profession?",
    options: ["Lawyer", "Doctor", "Architect", "Detective"],
    answer: "Lawyer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which country was Vincenzo Cassano raised before returning to Korea?",
    options: ["Italy", "United States", "Japan", "France"],
    answer: "Italy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the corrupt conglomerate that Vincenzo battles against?",
    options: [
      "The Babel Group",
      "The Han Corporation",
      "The Jang Group",
      "The Sun Group",
    ],
    answer: "The Babel Group",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the main female lead who partners with Vincenzo in his legal battles?",
    options: [
      "Hong Cha-young",
      "Jang Joo-sung",
      "Kim Seok-joo",
      "Choi Myung-hee",
    ],
    answer: "Hong Cha-young",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of building is the main setting for much of the series?",
    options: [
      "A law firm",
      "A high-rise apartment",
      "A law office",
      "A rooftop garden",
    ],
    answer: "A high-rise apartment",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Vincenzo's main objective upon returning to Korea?",
    options: [
      "To recover stolen gold",
      "To find his lost family",
      "To seek revenge",
      "To start a new life",
    ],
    answer: "To recover stolen gold",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the head of the Babel Group that Vincenzo targets?",
    options: [
      "Jang Joon-woo",
      "Jang Han-seok",
      "Jang Joo-sung",
      "Jang Seung-jae",
    ],
    answer: "Jang Han-seok",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the building that Vincenzo uses as his base of operations?",
    options: ["Geumga Plaza", "Babel Tower", "Seonghyeon Plaza", "Crown Tower"],
    answer: "Geumga Plaza",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which character is known for their skills in handling internal affairs within the Babel Group?",
    options: [
      "Jang Han-seok",
      "Choi Myung-hee",
      "Jang Joon-woo",
      "Nam Joo-sung",
    ],
    answer: "Choi Myung-hee",
  },
  {
    question: "What unique method does Vincenzo use to achieve his goals?",
    options: [
      "Legal manipulation",
      "Physical combat",
      "Bribery",
      "Political influence",
    ],
    answer: "Legal manipulation",
  },
];
